Guide to the Rock Music Catering papers, 1982-1985.
Rock Music Catering papers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Rock Music Catering papers, 1982-1985.
8592
Stageside Services.
1 cubic foot
Business and financial records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection consists of invoice books, ledger books, and 82 file folders documenting backstage catering for performers ranging across many musical genres: rock 'n roll, punk, heavy metal, R&B, Jazz, and country.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Stageside Services was a catering company based in Seattle, Washington. Owned and operated by Monica Di Meo, the company specialized in servicing catering needs for many of Seattle's music venues, such as the Music Hall Theater, Firehouse, Seattle Center Arena, Paramount, Eagles Hippodrome, and the Tacoma Dome. Stateside services provided primarily food and drink catering, but also laundry services and backstage furnishings. The company later added film productions to their scope of services.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection consists of 2 invoice books, 5 ledger books, and 82 file folders documenting backstage catering for performers ranging across many musical genres: rock 'n roll, punk, heavy metal, R&B, Jazz, and country. Files contain notes on food and dressing room requirements, a copy of the contract rider, miscellaneous receipts/invoices, and occasional notes or correspondence. Artists represented include Bon Jovi, David Bowie, Rick James, Joan Jett, Elton John, Judas Priest, the Kinks, Kool and the Gang, Madonna, Metallica, Motley Crue, Eddie Murphy, Tom Petty, Pink Floyd, the Police, the Pretenders, Queen, Lionel Ritchie, Rush, Talking Heads, James Taylor, Tina Turner, U2, Van Halen, and many others.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Stageside Services.
Subjects:
Caterers and catering -- Management.; Food service management.; Heavy metal; Musicians.; Musicians -- United States.; Punk rock music.; Rock music.; Rock music; Rhythm and blues music.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
File folders are organized by individual artist or band name.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Riders and catering information
Series II. Ledgers and receipt books
CONTAINER LIST
- Riders and catering information, 1982-1986
  Arranged alphabetically by band/performer.
  - Anamotion, 1985-03-26 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    Skootchie's.
  - Pat Benatar, 1983-03-22 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Hec Edmundson Pavillion
  - Blasters, 1984-09-15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bon Jovi, 1984-03-30 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Seattle Paramount
    Seattle, Washington
  - David Bowie, 1983-08-10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Tacoma Dome
    Tacoma, Washington
  - Cheap Trick/Rainbow, 1982-09-17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Seattle Center Arena
  - Miles Davis, 1985-09-22 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Seattle Paramount.
  - Neil Diamond, 1985-04-02 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    Seattle Coliseum.
  - Iron Maiden, 1984-12-10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Seattle Coliseum
  - Joe Jackson, 1984-05-15 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rick James, 1983-11-15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Jan and Dean, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mary Jane, 1985-11-22 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Jefferson Starship, 1986-02-15-1986-2-18 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Joan Jett, 1983-07-18 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Elton John, 1980-08-21 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Seattle Center
  - George Jones, 1985-06-29 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Howard Jones, 1985-07-10 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ricki Lee Jones, 1984-12-04 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Judas Priest, 1982-11-15 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gladys Knight, 1983-06-10 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Portland Paramount
    Portland, Oregon
  - Kidskin, 1985-11-4 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Mountaineer's Club
  - B.B. King, 1984-09-22 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - King Crimson, 1984-05-31 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Kinks, 1983-04-23-1985-02-28 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Kiss/Queensryche, 1985-02-13 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Seattle Arena
  - Kool and The Gang, 1984-06-05-1985-10-31 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Seattle Paramount, Seattle Arena, Northwest Airlines
  - Krokus/W.A.S.P./Helix, 1984-12-04 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Huey Lewis, 1984-04-11 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Little River Band, 1983-10-08-1985-05-21 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Kenny Loggins, 1982-10-14 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Los Lobos, 1985-03-16 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    H.U.B. Ballroom
  - Loverboy/Quiet Riot, 1983-07-15 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Loudness, 1985-04-28 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Moore Theatre
  - Lena Lovich, 1983-04-20 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Eagles Auditorium
  - Madonna, 1985-04-08 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Chuck Mangione, 1985-12-13 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Manhattan Transfer, 1984-07-20-1985-10-10 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Barry Manilow, 1985-09-10 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Men At Work, 1982-10-06-1982-10-12 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Seattle Paramount, Seattle Arena
  - Mike McDonald/Kenny G, 1985-12-09 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Metallica, 1985-03-17 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Pat Metheny, 1982-10-18-1984-10-27 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Seattle Paramount, Seattle Opera House
  - The Motels/Taxxi, 1982-10-11 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Eagles Hippodrome
  - Motley Crue, 1983-11-23 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Anne Murray, 1984-09-27-1984-09-28 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Eddie Murphy, 1985-05-12 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Wayne Newton, 1984-02-09 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Nightranger/Quarterflash, 1985-12-14 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Oingo Boingo, 1985-11-08 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Ozzy Osbourne/Motley Crue, 1982-06-14-1984-03-22 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Ted Nugent, 1984-3-11-1984-3-12 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Jeffrey Osborne, 1985-08-24 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Peter, Paul and Mary, 1985-09-19 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Tom Petty, 1983-04-08-1985-07-24 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Pink Floyd, 1983-03-18 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - The Police, 1982-09-01 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - The Police/The Fixx/The Thompson Twins, 1983-09-01 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Power Station, 1985-08-01 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - The Pretenders, 1984-02-22 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - John Prine, 1983-02-20 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Opera House
  - Psychedelic Furs, 1982-11-14-1984-08-10 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Queen, 1982-09-03 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Quiet Riot, 1984-10-07 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Bonnie Raitt, 1984-06-04 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Music Hall
  - Rank and File, 1984-06-14 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Ratt, 1984-08-20 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - U-2, 1983-05-26 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Raven/Wild Dogs/Metal Church, 1985-03-24 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - R.E.M., 1984-06-27-1985-07-12 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Music Hall, Seattle Paramount
  - Lionel Richie, 1984-07-03 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Joan Rivers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - The Romantics/Wang Chung, 1984-04-22 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Romeo Void, 1984-12-31 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Rush, 1984-05-18 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Scandal, 1983-02-25 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Scorpions, 1984-03-20-1985-08-29 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Seattle Coliseum, Tacoma Dome
    Seattle, Washington, Tacoma, Washington
  - Bob Seger, 1983-04-09 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Simple Minds, 1983-04-08-1984-06-13 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    Moore Theatre.
  - Russ Taft/David Mead, 1985-09-21 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    Fifth Avenue Theatre.
  - Talking Heads, 1983-12-02 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - James Taylor, 1984-05-05 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Tears for Fears, 1985-09-03 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Third World, 1982-07-24 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    Paramount Theatre
  - Thompson Twins, 1984-05-20-1985-11-13 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    Seattle Paramount, Seattle Center Arena
  - Tina Turner, 1985-09-29 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Twisted Sister/Tarzen, 1986-02-28 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Twisted Sister, 1984-09-29 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - UB-40, 1984-02-26-1985-02-23 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    Skoochie's, Moore Theatre..
  - Van Halen, 1982-09-02 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Stevie Ray Vaughn/Widow, 1984-06-20 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Weird Al Yankovic, 1984-06-15 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Ledgers and receipt books, 1983-1987
  Ledgers contain names of bands and dates of events.
  - Stageside Services, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Stageside Services, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Stageside Services Sales Booklet, 1987-07-21-1987-10-02 (Box 1)
  - Stageside Services Invoice Booklet, 1987-08-14-1987-08-22 (Box 1)
  - Stageside Services Invoice Booklet, 1987-08-22-1987-10-02 (Box 1)
  - Ledger, 1983-01-20-1983-12-13 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    Blue cover, in folder
  - Ledger, 1983-02-17-1983-12-31 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    Red cover, in folder
  - Ledger, 1984-01-10-1984-08-06 (Box 1)
    Blue cover
  - Ledger, 1984-01-22-1984-07-26 (Box 1)
    Black cover
  - Ledger, 1984-01-22-1984-08-08 (Box 1)
    Red cover